edwinwatts.com 2014-03-27

# Privacy Policy - Golf Clubs, Drivers, Irons, Hybrids, Wedges, Golf Shoes and Golf Equipment at Edwin Watts Golf

At Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of any personal information you provide to us. This Privacy Policy explains our policies and practices for collecting, storing, using, sharing, and protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect through this Web site, through your purchases of our products wherever they are sold, and through marketing and promotional activities that we conduct from time to time.

Along with our Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy governs your use of our Web site. We may update this Privacy Policy as we continue to improve the services, products, and features we provide to you and as new developments in technology, law, or regulation call for changes. Please check this Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you stay current.

**How Your Information Is Collected and Used**

When you purchase items from us or voluntarily submit information to us (for example, when you sign up for an account with Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company, send us e-mails or subscribe to our e-mail promotions, participate in sweepstakes, contests, or surveys, or post information on our Web site), we may collect personally identifiable information from you such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, and credit card number. We may use this information to provide you with the products and services you have requested, to investigate and answer questions or concerns you submit to us, to offer you opportunities to participate in promotional programs tailored to you, to list you as a winner of a contest or sweepstakes, or to notify you of information that may be of interest to you about Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company or our business partners and affiliates.

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information from you, (such as information regarding your interests, hobbies, preferences for products and services, and lifestyle) when you choose to provide it.

When you visit our Web site, we and our third-party service providers use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie" to identify you and enhance your experience on the site in various ways, such as by remembering your user name, password, and preferences, and tracking your click streams. Cookies are small files placed on your computer's hard drive. We and our third-party service providers use cookies and pixel tags to collect certain technical information from your computer when you visit our Web site, including your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, your computer's operating system, your browser type, and any referring Web site address. Most Internet browsers give you the option to reject cookies, but doing so generally hinders the browser's performance and will adversely affect your experience when using our Web site.

We partner with third-party Internet advertising companies, known as "ad networks," to serve ads for us across the Internet. Ad networks use cookies and pixel tags to collect information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites so that they can deliver ads to you that may correspond to your interests. We do not share any personally identifiable information about you with these ad networks. If you prefer not to receive these ads, you may opt-out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's opt-out page, at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

We may also obtain information about you from third parties, including demographic information (such as number of household members, age, and gender), and purchase preferences. We use such information to improve the accuracy of our customer database, increase our understanding of our customers, and identify potential customers.

**How Your Information May Be Shared**

We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to outside marketers. We may, however, share such information in limited circumstances, outlined below.

We may share your information with our subsidiaries, affiliates, and trusted businesses partners, so that we, and they, can provide products and services you have requested and information and offers that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may share your information with third parties that need access to the information to help us fulfill your requests for products and services. We require all parties with whom we share this information to comply with our standards of quality and to comply with our policies for safeguarding your information.

When we collect aggregate data that does not include personally identifiable information, such as demographic and statistical information, we may share that data with third parties.

We may disclose your information when we believe any applicable law, regulation, or legal proceeding requires us to do so, or when disclosure is necessary to respond to claims against us, to protect our customers, to report or collect debts owed to us, or otherwise to protect our rights and property.

If Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company becomes involved in a merger, reorganization, or bankruptcy, we may transfer or otherwise share your information in connection with that transaction or event.   

**How Your Information Is Safeguarded**

We enforce reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect against any unauthorized access to or disclosure of your information. We maintain your information on a secured server behind a firewall. All data is encrypted, and all data related to our retail services is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer technology. Even as we strive to protect your information, however, we cannot guarantee that these or any other information security measures will be completely effective, and we cannot assume responsibility for the actions of parties who may gain unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. Thus, Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company makes no warranties, express, implied, or otherwise, as to the ultimate effectiveness of our reasonable and appropriate security measures.

**Third-Party Web Sites**

Our Web site may carry advertisements by third parties and links to the Web sites of third parties, so that we can make additional products, services, and information available to you. This Privacy Policy applies only to Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company, and we do not control the privacy policies and practices of third parties, which may differ from ours. Because third parties may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect their own data, or make their own solicitations of personal information from you, we encourage you to read their privacy policies before using their Web sites. We assume no responsibility for your sharing of information with these third parties. 

**Accessing and Updating Personal Information**

When you register with Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company LoyalTee Rewards® program, you can review, maintain, and change your own account information at any time. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we also depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Promotional e-Mails**

To provide you with information about special sales, promotions, and other offers that may be of interest to you, Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company may, from time to time, send you promotional e-mails if you choose to opt into receiving such e-mails. If at any time you choose not to receive these promotional e-mails any longer, you can unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each promotional e-mail. Please be advised that you may continue to receive e-mails from us until your requested change takes effect.

**Children's Privacy**

Our Web site is a general audience site, and we do not intentionally collect or store any personally identifiable information from children. Nevertheless, we take special precautions with children's privacy, including following the federal guidelines set by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). In compliance with COPPA, we will not actively seek personal information about children under the age of 13 without the permission of their parent or legal guardian. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe that child has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, you may contact us to review and request deletion of the information. For security purposes, you must provide sufficient identifying information for us to verify that you are the child's parent or guardian. At your request, we will make all reasonable efforts to delete the information provided.

**LoyalTee Rewards Program Terms and Conditions**

Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company's Rewards Program participation and its benefits are offered at the sole discretion of Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company. Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company has the right to modify, add or delete any of the Program rules, terms, conditions, benefits or rewards, in whole or in part, at any time, with or without notice, even though such changes may affect the value of accumulated points, the value of the LoyalTee Rewards and/or the time for redemption. The Program has no predetermined termination date and may continue until such time as Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company, in its sole discretion, elects to designate a Program termination date. Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company has the right to end the Program at any time without providing written notice to you. Participation in the Program is void if prohibited by law in the jurisdiction in which the prospective participant resides. If in any particular state the Program or Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company has to apply for any special license, bonding, permit or other governmental regulatory approval, the Program will be void in that particular state. 

**California Privacy Rights**

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, California residents have the right to request information about how we share certain kinds of personal information with third parties. California law gives you, as our customer, the right to receive the following information from us: 

  * The categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing during the preceding calendar year;
  * The names and addresses of the third parties that received that information and, for any third-party business for which the name does not reveal the nature of the business, examples of the products or services marketed by that business.

We may provide this information in a standard format that is not specific to you. You may request this information by contacting us by clicking on the following link: [Service Center](mailto:service_team@wattsgolf.com?subject=Service)

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, as dictated by new developments in business, technology, law, or regulation. Any changes will take effect as soon as they are posted. Please check this Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you stay current. Your continued used of this Web site after we post any revision to the Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised policy.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us in one of the following ways:

  * By calling us, at 1-800-874-0146
  * By visiting us at www.edwinwattsgolf.com and selecting the "Contact Us" link
  * By writing to us at Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company, 20 Hill Avenue NW, Fort Walton Beach, FL 32548-3858, Attention: Internet Department, Privacy Policy Team.

Copyright © 2014 Edwin Watts Golf a Worldwide Golf Company Shops, LLC
